(Bernadette:)That was ten years ago.
(Sheldon:)Nine years, 11 months
and three weeks ago,
(Sheldon:)he followed that up by replacing
the slides for my lecture
(Sheldon:)with photographs
of nude fat women bending over.
(Amy:)Really?
(Howard:)The lecture was on
cosmic gas clouds.
That's funny!
(Raj:)I was there. It was funny.
(Sheldon:)In any event, that began
a decade-long progression
(Sheldon:)of insults, pranks and
unwanted magazine subscriptions.
(Sheldon:)To this day,
I still get a monthly copy
(Sheldon:)of Granny on Granny.
(Sheldon:)Which, other than its
surprisingly fun puzzle page,
(Sheldon:)is complete filth.
(Amy:)Thanks for walking me
to my car.
(Raj:)Actually, it's for both of us.
(Raj:)Last night, I watched
West Side Story,
(Raj:)and I'm a little freaked out
by street gangs.
(Amy:)Why can't Raj find a girl?
The mystery continues.